Sight is survival.
Unseen is a horror, mystery film directed by Yoko Okumura.
Sam receives a call from Emily, a near blind woman who is
running from her murderous ex in the woods.
Can she survive using Sam as her eyes via video call?
Carol, played by Missi Pyle.
Sam, played by Jolene Purdy.
Emily, played by Midori Francis.
Charlie, played by Michael Patrick Lane.
Isaac, played by Nicholas X. Parsons.
Carl, played by Brett Baker.
Unseen is a 2023 American horror thriller film directed by Yoko Okumura in her feature
directorial debut, and written by Salvatore Cardoni and Brian Rawlins.
The film stars Midori Francis, Jolene Purdy and Missi Pyle.
Jason Blum serves as an executive producer under
his Blumhouse Television banner.
The plot follows gas station clerk Sam who receives a call from Emily, a nearly
blind woman who is running from her murderous ex in the woods.
Emily must survive the ordeal with Sam being her
eyes from afar using a video call.
The film was digitally released in the United States on March
7, 2023, to positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of gas station, woods, cat and
mouse, blind woman, psychological horror.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.